(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ライブグッズ2次販売決定!! 11.19 公演終了後〜
Live goods 2nd sale confirmed!! Available after the performance on Nov 19th.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
アニメにハマって、歌いたくなっちゃった。
I got hooked on anime, and I just had to sing.
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて…
To be able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてつらい！
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
ねえ、今日はどこ行く？
Hey, where are we going today?
Yahoo! カーナビ、
Yahoo! Car Navigation,
推しドラ、好評販売中！
Oshi-dora is now on sale!
今ならダブル購入で、
Buy both now,
ぺこあず限定ボイスも聞けちゃう！
and you can hear the exclusive PekoAzu voice!
AZKiと一緒に、
Together with AZKi,
ドライブしよ？
let's go for a drive!
推しドラで検索！
Search for Oshi-dora!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定！！ 11.19 公演終了後〜
Live Goods 2nd Round Sales Confirmed! Starting after the 11.19 performance.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Please wait a moment until the concert starts.
Attention: 演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定!!
Live Goods 2nd batch sales decided!!
11.19 公演終了後〜
Starting after the performance on Nov 19th.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Attention: To our guests.
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production.
Cheering loudly is OK.
ライブグッズ 2次販売決定!!
11.19 公演終了後〜
Live Goods 2nd Sale Decided!!
Starting 11.19 after the performance finishes.
本日は AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure" にご来場いただきありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure" today!
うわ〜！
Wow!
こんこんこんこん 小豆！
Kon-kon-kon-kon Ko-AZKi!
あ、みんな元気がいいですね
Oh, everyone is full of energy!
右手にマイク、左手に地図、あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー！ AZKiです！
Mic in my right hand, map in my left, Zero-Guesser for your heart! I'm AZKi!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live concert until the end, I have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and video recording during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member immediately.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど...
Moshing, diving, throwing objects onto the stage...
他の人の迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
...or any acts that annoy others or interfere with the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って、盛り上がってください！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
はーい！
Okay!
えらい！
Good job!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り...
Also, please be aware that cameras for streaming and photography are present...
客席が映り込む場合があります。
...and the audience may be captured in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
はーい！
Okay!
えらい！
Good job!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、「#AZKiと未来へ」です。
Also, the hashtag for the live concert is "#AZKiAndToTheFuture".
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しい！お願いします！
I'd be happy if you use the hashtag to hype it up! Please!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Now then, it's almost time for the show to start.
みんなの声、いっぱい聞かせてね！
Let me hear your voices loud and clear!
Ah...
鏡よ 教えて 私の...
Mirror, tell me, my...
世にあるのだろう
Does it exist in this world?
分からない
I don't know...
分からないよ
I really don't know.
周りと比べたってさ
Comparing myself to those around me...
虚しくなるだけ
...only makes me feel empty.
あの椅子が
That chair...
海鳴りのように
...like the rumbling of the sea,
涙を奪う
steals away my tears.
切り取った風景を
I'll take this scenery I've cut out...
道標にしよう
...and make it my guidepost.
そうだ
That's right.
傷ついた感情も
Even my wounded emotions...
連れて行くから
...I'll bring them along with me.
そっと響くファンファーレが
The softly resounding fanfare...
新しい未来を感じてる
...makes me feel a new future.
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ
Even if I'm scared, I must move forward.
どこまでも
No matter how far.
届けこの祈りよ光となれ
Reach out, oh prayer, and become light.
もっと もっと
More, more.
少しずつでもいい
Even little by little is fine.
私という答えを
Find the answer that is "me".
もっと
More...
不安だよ教えて
I'm anxious, please tell me.
私の証は
Will the proof of my existence...
輝けるのかな
...be able to shine?
見つけたい
I want to find it.
見つけたいよ
I really want to find it.
誰かの地図をなぞるは
Tracing someone else's map...
苦しくなるだけ
...only becomes painful.
迷いもいつも
Even my hesitation, always...
力に変えるよ
...I'll turn into strength.
心に誓う
I swear to my heart.
錆びついた運命の
The rusted gears of fate...
歯車を回そう
...let's make them turn.
ほら
Look.
着飾った感情は
My dressed-up emotions...
脱ぎ捨てるから
...I'll cast them aside.
そっと紡いだストーリーへ
To the gently spun story...
叶えたい願いを信じてる
...I believe in the wish I want to grant.
胸を張って歌うしかないでしょ
I have to stand tall and sing.
全力で
With all my might.
ネガティブなもの歌に変わる
Negative things will turn into song.
今でもっともっと
Now, more and more...
悩みながらでいい
...it's okay to be troubled.
全てが宝物
Everything is a treasure.
みんな！今日は楽しんでいってね！
Everyone! Enjoy yourselves today!
いつの日かこの声を受け取ってくれたなら
If someday you receive this voice of mine...
この言葉を君に
...I'll give these words to you.
もう大丈夫 ひとりじゃない
"It's okay now, you're not alone."
強い想いを繋ぐよ
I'll connect these strong feelings.
一歩踏み出してみた
I tried taking a step forward...
優しく世界は微笑む
...and the world smiled gently.
高鳴る気持ちに身を任せて
Surrender to the throbbing feelings.
さあ行こう
Let's go.
そっと響くファンファーレが
The softly resounding fanfare...
新しい未来を感じてる
...makes me feel a new future.
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ
Even if I'm scared, I must move forward.
どこまでも
No matter how far.
届けこの祈りよ光となれ
Reach out, oh prayer, and become light.
もっと もっと
More, more.
少しずつでもいい
Even little by little is fine.
私という答えを
Find the answer that is "me".
もっと
More...
この扉の向こうが
If what lies beyond this door...
未開の可能性なら
...is unexplored possibility,
今を動かせるの
then I can move the present.
暗闇を手探りで
Fumbling through the darkness,
不安と焦燥の中
amidst anxiety and impatience...
零れる光を見た
...I saw spilling light.
手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand...
時を超えて
Transcending time,
繋がるよ 心が今
our hearts connect right now.
想像するの 私のストーリー
I'll create my own story.
五感を響かせて
Resonating with all five senses,
君を知りたいから
because I want to know you.
輝かせよう 新しい世界
Let's make this new world shine.
生まれた意味を
Finding the meaning of
見つけることさ
why I was born.
全てが始まる この場所で
Everything starts here in this place.
声が枯れるまで 叫んで
Shout until my voice runs dry!
答え教えてよ Dear Melancholy
Tell me the answer, Dear Melancholy.
Yeah
Woo
身体と感情が交差する
Body and emotions intersect.
正しい自分は何？
What is the correct "me"?
2と3を繋いで交差する
Connecting 2(D) and 3(D), they cross.
世界は一つじゃない
The world is not just one.
いいねとファボの数字 増えていく
The numbers of likes and favs are increasing.
盲目に正論振りかざして 首を絞める
Blindly brandishing correct arguments, choking myself.
私の生きる世界は
Let me choose the world I live in
自分の手で選ばせてよ
with my own hands.
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight Melancholy.
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
A reborn identity.
この身が この辺が 痛いよ
This body, right here... it hurts.
うわべ面の泣きストーリー
A superficial sob story,
収束してく可愛いフェイス
a cute face that converges.
私を
Will I...
will I...
誰かにとって変わるの？
be replaced by someone else?
どんどん行くよ！
We're keeping it going!
みんな手高く上げて！
Everyone, hands up high!
はい！
Hey!
どうして気づいてしまったの
Why did I end up realizing it?
熱くなるほどに
The more passionate I become...
隠しきれない戸惑い
Confusion I can't fully hide,
ぎこちない距離
an awkward distance.
あやふやな視線
With a vague gaze,
揺れる心 バレないように
I try not to let my wavering heart be seen.
人知れず響く 胸の鼓動
My heartbeat resonates in secret.
呼吸さえ儘ならないのに
Even though I can't even breathe properly,
きっと何処かで願っているんだ
surely I'm wishing for it somewhere.
終わりのない時間を
For an endless time.
恋の始まりは誰も知らない
No one knows the beginning of love.
私だけの宝物
It's my very own treasure.
少しでも言葉にしたら
If I put even a little into words,
陽だまりのような笑顔も
that smile like a sunny spot,
土砂降りの涙も 全部
and all the pouring tears...
無くしてしまいそうで
I feel like I might lose them all.
もしも！
If...!
もしも一つだけ叶うのならば
If just one wish could come true,
ただ君のすぐ隣で
I'd just want to be right by your side,
過ぎてゆく季節眺めていたい
watching the seasons pass by.
溢れそうなほどの想いは
These feelings about to overflow,
胸の奥にしまい込んだ
I tucked them deep inside my chest.
二人の声が空に
Our voices are being sucked
吸い込まれてく
into the sky.
閉ざした世界
In a closed world,
微かに聞こえる音
a faint sound is heard.
世界で二人 切り取られた
The two of us were cut out from the world.
届きそうな手
Hands that seem like they could reach,
すれ違った心が
hearts that missed each other,
ちょっと痛んだ
ached a little.
ここで待って
Wait here...
決めなくちゃね
I have to decide.
今 儘で
As things are now,
戸惑い溢れてしまうよ
confusion will just overflow.
溺れた想いを数えて
Counting the drowned feelings.
何度も繰り返した世界 世界
The world, the world repeated again and again.
開くの待っている
Waiting for it to open.
まだまだ盛り上がっていくよ！
We're going to get even more hyped!
もっと声出せるよね？
You can scream louder, right?
馬鹿馬鹿しいな 不自由な思考
How ridiculous, this restrained thinking.
意味がないなら 楽しんだもん
If it's meaningless, might as well enjoy it.
攻めてく人
People attacking.
逃げてく人
People running away.
良くない人に生きる資格はない？
Do bad people have no right to live?
前向きな夢
Positive dreams.
狂った世界で僕らはみんな生きてるから
Because we are all living in a crazy world.
好きになったりどうして愛
Falling in love, why love?
祈りのように
Like a prayer.
ニュースで流れる大事件に
For the big incidents on the news...
涙を流す人はいない
...no one sheds tears.
ビルジェンガ嘘の街から
From the city of lies built like Jenga...
抜け出して
...escape.
光の街へ
To the city of light.
メドレーラスト！
Medley Last!
Fake Fake Fake...
偽物ばかり全て
Only fakes, everything.
上辺で飾って誤魔化して
Decorating the surface and deceiving.
何が善悪か分かんないから
I don't know what is good or evil...
壊れていく
...so it's breaking down.
一体何が本当なんだっけ
What was the truth again?
期待しては裏切られて
Expecting and being betrayed.
馬鹿だ嘘は泣いて死んじゃうよ
Idiot, lies, crying and dying.
こんな異常だらけの世界で
In a world full of abnormalities like this...
存在探してるんだ
...searching for existence.
絶望のない自由なリアル
A free reality without despair...
どこにもないですか
...is it nowhere to be found?
こんな異常だらけの世界で
In a world full of abnormalities like this...
存在探してるんだ
...searching for existence.
何を言われても
No matter what is said.
満たされることないよ
I won't be satisfied.
感覚ずれて
Senses are off.
全て忘れて
Forget everything.
はい！えーということで！
Okay! Um, so!
AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 "Departure"へようこそ！
Welcome to AZKi SOLO LiVE 2025 'Departure'!
ちょっとぶっ飛ばしすぎた。
I went a bit too hard.
歌いすぎました。
I sang too much.
ああ、見渡す限り開拓者！
Ah, as far as I can see, Pioneers!
本当に、もうでもこの景色を見て
Really, seeing this view...
もう感極まってしまっているんですが
...I'm already overwhelmed with emotion, but...
みんな本当に今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
...thank you all so much for coming today!
今日はAZKiにとって初めてのアリーナでのソロライブです。
Today is AZKi's first solo live at an Arena.
この景色本当にもう胸がいっぱいで
This view really fills my heart...
まだまだまだ早いか、まだこの涙は。
...no, it's still, still, still too early for these tears.
ということで、みんな今日はね
So, thank you everyone...
貴重な一日をこのAZKiのライブのために
...for taking time out of your precious day for this AZKi live.
時間を作ってくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for making the time.
早速なんですが、えーぶっ飛ばしましたね、メドレー。
Straight away, um, I went hard with the medley, didn't I?
どうでした？
How was it?
ありがとうございます。そしてねもちろん一曲目は
Thank you. And of course, for the first song...
この曲と決めていました「未来カンパネラ」。
...I decided it had to be this one, 'Mirai Campanella'.
ということで、新EPから、えーと
So, from the new EP, um...
Re:Startからね、一曲お届けしましたが
...from Re:Start, I delivered one song, but...
みんなEPは聴いてくれましたか？
...did everyone listen to the EP?
そしてそして、本日の衣装、どうですか？
And, and, how is today's outfit?
早速ね、そのキービジュアルでみんなは
I think everyone thought based on the key visual...
この衣装が来るんじゃないかと思ってたと思うんですけど
...that this outfit would appear right away, but...
なんと！
Surprisingly!
衣装も作っていただきました
I had this outfit made too.
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
そして、今日のね素敵なステージでございます
And, we have this wonderful stage today.
みんな上部の装飾気づきました？
Did everyone notice the decorations up top?
変化してたの気づきました？この上のね
Did you notice they changed? Up here.
この今、アルファっていう
Right now, this "Alpha"...
あ、ピカピカピカ
Ah, sparkle sparkle sparkle.
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
この変化気づきましたでしょうか
Did you notice this change?
曲のね頭で実は
Actually, at the beginning of the song,
あの... このアルファの装飾部分がですね
Um... this Alpha decoration part...
あの、色が変わってまして
Uh, the color changed,
みんなちょっと、あの... ついてくの大変だったよね
It was probably a bit hard for everyone to keep up, right?
この色にしてくださいっていう
"Please change to this color," it was signaling,
ペンライトカラーになっておりました
It had become the penlight color.
本当に曲の冒頭の方なので
It's really right at the start of the song, so...
あの... 見れた方は
Uh... for those who managed to see it,
ありがとう
Thank you.
あの、変えていただけたらなと思います
I hope you can change your lights to match.
それに合わせてね、みんなもペンライト点灯していただいたり
Matching that, everyone turning on your penlights...
2色光った時はですね、ペンライトも2色にしてください
When two colors light up, please make your penlights two colors too.
みんなで一緒に今日のライブ作ってこう！
Let's create today's live together!
よろしくお願いします
Let's do this!
お願いします
Please!
ということで
So,
えー今日のライブはですね
Uh, for today's live,
え、バンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしております
We are bringing it to you with the band members!
すごい素晴らしい演奏ありがとうございます
Amazing, wonderful performance, thank you.
しかもなんと
And what's more,
え、今回はですね
Uh, this time,
バイオリンも参加しております
We have a violin participating too!
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
えー今日のために、えー特別にアレンジした楽曲もたくさんあるので
There are many songs specially arranged just for today, so...
お楽しみに
Look forward to it!
そして、今日はね現地の想い出だけじゃなくてですね
And, today is not just about memories for those at the venue,
配信で見てくれる開拓者もいます
There are Pioneers watching via stream too!
配信のみんなー！
Everyone on the stream—!
わー！
Wah—!
はい、コメントも見えてるよー
Yes, I can see your comments too!
うおーイエーイ
Whoa, yay!
あずきー、ふーイエーイ
AZKi—, whoo, yay!
バイオリンがすごい！
"The violin is amazing!"
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
ということで
So,
本日は
Today,
えー... ハッシュタグ
Uh... with the hashtag...
#AZKiと未来へ で
#ToTheFutureWithAZKi
今日の感想や、え、印象に残った瞬間を
Your thoughts on today, or, uh, memorable moments...
ポストしてください
Please post them.
後で全部見に行きます
I'll go look at them all later.
よろしくー！
Please do!
配信のみんなスクショもよろしくー
Stream folks, screenshots too please!
そして、皆様
And, everyone,
YouTubeやTikTokでご覧の皆様
Everyone watching on YouTube or TikTok,
残念だ...
It's unfortunate...
早い早い早い
Fast, fast, fast!
えー、無料チラ見せはここまで！
Uh, the free sneak peek ends here!
えーー！
Ehh—!
ありがとうございます、現地の「えー」もいただきまして
Thank you, I received the "Ehh" from the venue too.
え、まだまだ、え一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは
Uh, for those who still want to get hyped together,
え、概要欄のリンクから
Uh, from the link in the description,
配信サイトへ飛べますので
You can jump to the streaming site, so...
ここからが本番なので
The real show starts from here, so...
たくさんの方に見ていただきたいなと思っています
I hope many people will watch.
え、今回のライブなんですが
Uh, regarding this live,
これまでAZKiが歩んできた軌跡
The path AZKi has walked until now,
そしてこれから歩んでいく未来
And the future I will walk from now on,
その全てをみんなと一緒に一つの物語として
All of that, together with everyone, as one story...
繋いでいくような一日にしたいと思っています
I want to make it a day where we connect it all.
え、このライブで私の「今」
Uh, in this live, my "now"...
の全てを音楽と共に
Everything of it, together with music,
え、まっすぐみんなに届けていきます
Uh, I will deliver it straight to everyone.
よろしくお願いします
Please treat me well!
それじゃあ、どんどんいきますよ
Alright then, let's keep going!
最後まで一緒に楽しんでいこうね！
Let's enjoy it together until the end!
一緒に歌おう！
Let's sing together!
みんなの声聞かせて！
Let me hear everyone's voices!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました。
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!